别太担心
Don't look so worried.
这是我的活儿
It's my job.
才不是呢 你是个家庭主妇
No, it's not. You're a housewife.
是吗 臭小子
Yeah, punk?
你在这儿看到我的房子了吗
You see my house around here?
还家庭主妇呢
A housewife.
它们没有妈妈
They don't have a mother.
也许她在其他地方
She might be somewhere else.
也许被吃掉了
Maybe she got eaten.
每个东西都是其他东西的食物
Everything is food for something else.
《行尸走肉》
你还能表现得再明显点儿不
Could you be more obvious?
拿着 尽情享用吧
Here, enjoy.
你想用水果封我的口吗
Are you trying to buy my silence with fruit?
当然不止了 还有肉干
Of course not. There's also jerky.
你能告诉我
Will you please tell me why.
你爸为什么要把行尸秘密地关在仓库里吗
your dad has a secret barn full of walkers?
- 这太惊悚了 - 小声点
- It's creepy. - Shh.
- 你知道的 对吧 - 别说了
- You know that, right? - Shh.
你只要相信我就行了 好吗
Just trust me on this, okay?
但是我不擅长说谎
But I suck at lying.
我甚至不能玩扑克牌 跟说谎没两样
I can't even play poker. It's too much like lying.
你得对这事保密
You have to keep this to yourself.
你必须这么做 求你了
You have to. Please.
戴尔 给你些桃子
Dale, here's some peaches for you.
谢谢啦
Mm, thank you.
- 早啊 - 早
- Morning. - Morning.
- 怎么了 - 没咋
- What's up? - Nothing.
啥事也没有 怎么了
Nothing's up. Why?
在啊
Hey.
这本书不怎么好看 但是…
This is not that great, but…
咋了 因为没插图么
What, no pictures?
抱歉 我感觉糟透了
I'm so sorry. I feel like shit.
是啊 我也是
Yeah, you and me both.
我不奢望你能原谅我
I don't expect you to forgive me,
但是 如果有任何我能做的事…
But if there's anything I can do…
你只是想保护大家
You were trying to protect the group.
我们没事
We're good.
但是
But hey,
如果你再击中我 你最好祈祷我死了
shoot me again, and you'd best pray I'm dead.
瑞克怎么说
What did Rick say?
你没告诉他吗
You didn't tell him?
好吧
Okay.
但是你必须得告诉他
But you have to.
你怀孕了
You're pregnant.
你得补充维生素 药物
You need vitamins, medicine,
还需要个舒服的枕头
a nice pillow.
拿着
Here.
你把我的这份也吃了吧
You can have my share.
亲爱的 我不想要你的食物 行不
Honey, I don't want your food, okay?
你自己吃
Eat.
你必须得吃东西 你太瘦了
You need to eat. You're too skinny.
如果你不让瑞克照顾你
And if you're not gonna let.
就必须得让别人照顾你
Rick take care of you, then someone has to.
洛莉 你身体有问题
Lori, you have a medical condition.
我会再去一次城里
I'll make another run into town.
告诉我你还需要什么
Just tell me what you need.
我要你保守秘密
I need you to be quiet about this.
行吗 求你了
All right? Please.
桃子男
Hey! Peach man.
这条溪水往南流
The creek flows south,
经过达里尔找到的那个农舍
past that farmhouse Daryl found.
也许索菲亚在这儿掉了娃娃
Maybe Sophia dropped the doll there,
然后顺水往下被冲到了这里
The current brought it downstream.
这么说 你认为她
So what, you think she.
走了这条路然后北上了
took this road here and then she went north?
是的 那条路什么情况
Yeah. What's up that way?
是个住宅开发区
A housing development.
大概十年前就有了
It went in maybe 10 years ago.
射击练习完后 去一趟那里
Take a run up there after gun practice.
我负责这里 但是你得找个人做后援
I'll hold down the fort here, but take backup.
达里尔出了这事后
After what went down with daryl,
我不希望任何人单独行动
I don't want anyone going out alone.
我们两人一组
We stay in pairs.
我会考虑找个搭档
I'll take suggestions on a partner.
看看他们在靶场表现如何
See how they do on the range,
再自己挑人吧
then take your pick.
谢谢
Thanks.
我的望远镜呢
My binoculars.
哦对 在这儿
Yeah yeah.
好了 再见
Okay, bye.
我们想参加今天的射击训练
We'd like to join you for gun training today.
赫谢尔说的很清楚
Hershel's been very clear.
没经过他同意
I can't involve any of you.
我不能让你们任何一人掺和进来
in what we do without his okay.
他不喜欢这么做 但还是同意了
He doesn't like it, but he consented.
我们中只有奥蒂斯会用枪
Otis was the only one who knew guns.
既然他不在了
Now that he's gone,
我们得学会保护自己
we gotta learn to protect ourselves.
她爸也是从这方面考虑的
Her father saw the sense in that.
无意冒犯 但我得去亲自问问赫谢尔
No offense, but I'll ask Hershel myself.
伙计 帽子不错啊
Dude, nice lid, man.
怎么了
What's going on?
我也想学射击
I want to learn to shoot too.
你能教我吗
Can you teach me?
伙计 这个得看你爸妈的意思
Well, man, that's… that's up to your parents.
你能跟他们讲吗 他们会听你的
Can you talk to them? They'll listen to you.
再说吧 好吗
We'll see, okay?
等等
Hey.
让我看看你那儿是什么
Let me see what you've got there.
这是怎么回事
How the hell did this happen?
都怪我 我让他进了房车
Well, it's my fault. I let him into the R.V.
他说他想到处走走 还说你同意的
He said he wanted a walkie, that you sent him for one.
所以总的来说 他撒谎了
So on top of everything else, he lied.
他在想些什么
What's he thinking?
他想学用枪 他让我教他
He wants to learn how to shoot. He asked me to teach him.
虽然这不关我事
Now it's none of my business,
但我很乐意教他 看你们的了
But I'm happy to do it. It's your call.
我不赞成
I'm not comfortable with it.
别让我唱黑脸好吗 瑞克
Oh, don't make me out to be the unreasonable one here. Rick?
我懂 我也有顾虑 但是
I know. I have my concerns too, but…
没什么但是 他才刚受了枪伤
There's no but. He was just shot.
刚刚复原 现在却想拿枪
He's just back on his feet and he wants a gun?
总比他怕枪好
Better than him being afraid of 'em.
营地里有枪是有原因的
There are guns in camp for a reason.
他得学会怎样安全使用
He should learn to handle them safely.
我才不想我儿子拿着枪到处走
I don't want my kid walking around with a gun.
那你怎么辩解这事
But how can you defend that?
你让他没保护措施就到处乱走
You can't let him go around without protection.
他只要一直待这儿就很安全
He's as safe as he'll ever be right here.
听着 你说的一切
Look, everything you're saying.
都有道理 但感觉不妥
makes perfect sense. It feels wrong.
我是说 之前他跟着你去林子里
I mean I didn't feel good.
我就有不祥的感觉
about him following you out into the woods.
我真希望我当时会说些什么
And I wish I'd said something.
我应该坚持的
I should've gone with my gut.
他长大了 谢天谢地
He's growing up, thank god.
我们得把他当成年人对待
We've got to start treating him more like an adult.
那他也得表现得像个成年人啊
Then he needs to act like one.
他还不够成熟来用枪
He's not mature enough to handle a gun.
我不会拿着玩的 妈妈
I'm not gonna play with it, mom.
枪不是玩具
It's not a toy.
抱歉我让你失望了
I'm sorry I disappointed you,
但是我想去找索菲亚
but I want to look for Sophia.
我想保护我们的营地
and I want to defend our camp.
不用枪我没法做到这些
I can't do that without a gun.
肖恩是我所知道最好的教练
Shane's the best instructor I know.
我见过他教比卡尔还小的孩子
I've seen him teach kids younger than Carl.
你一定要认真对待
You will take this seriously.
为自己的行为负责任
and you will behave responsibly.
如果有任何一个人和我说
And if I hear from anyone in this camp.
你做了我们不希望你做的事情
that you're not living up to our expectations…
他不会让你失望的
He won't let you down.
是的
Yeah.
如果你要这么做 就得听肖恩的指挥
Now if you're gonna do this, you listen to Shane.
- 好的 爸爸 - 好吗 要小心
- Okay, dad. - All right? You be careful.
- 你来吗 - 我得去帮戴尔
- You coming? - I gotta help Dale.
清理房车上的火花塞
clean the spark plugs on the R.V.
他说要给我讲讲机械原理
He said he's gonna teach me mechanics.
我应该去找他
I should probably go look for him.
我在这
You found me.
他是个好学生
He's a good learner.
火花塞 是吗
Spark plugs, huh?
想告诉我怎么回事吗
Want to tell me what's going on?
你年长
You're old.
经验丰富
You're… you know things.
所以
So.
如果有人告诉你某件事
What if somebody told you something.
这件事另一个人应该知道
that somebody else should know…?
格伦 别吞吞吐吐的 快说
Glenn, stop being dramatic. Spit it out.
谷仓里有行尸
There's… there's walkers in the barn.
还有洛莉怀孕了
and Lori's pregnant.
得了吧 老兄别打的那么烂啊
Hey, come on, man. Don't give me that gangsta shit.
漂亮
Good work.
别灰心
Don't be discouraged.
你一定会打中的
You'll hit the target eventually.
谁说我没打中
Who says I didn't hit my target?
试试这把 要沉一些
Try this one. It's heavy.
更容易平衡 两次机会
You get better balance, twice the rounds.
她掌握门道了
I'd say she's got the hang of it.
够格学习高级课程
I'd say she's ready for the advanced class.
其他人回去之后
It might be worth your while.
我们再开始训练
after the rest of us head back to camp.
好的 当然可以
Sure. Why not?
- 感觉如何 - 我喜欢它的重量
- How's it feeling? - I like the weight.
你决定不走了
So you decided not to leave us.
改变主意了吗
Something change your mind?
- 打中了 - 非常棒
- Got it. - That's a great shot.
胆小鬼奈利
Nervous Nelly?
它自己回来了
She find her way home?
今天早上在它的马圈里发现了它
Found her in her stall this morning.
我喜欢你的农场
I love your fields.
今早我走了很长时间
Took a long walk this morning.
最后走到了谷仓
I ended up by the barn.
我听见了行尸的声音
I heard the moans.
那真不幸
That's unfortunate.
我相信你保守这个秘密肯定有原因
I'm sure you have your reasons for keeping this a secret.
广播停止前 我一直在看
I saw the broadcasts before they stopped,
看到了人们疯狂的恐惧 残忍
saw the irrational fear, the atrocities,
就像在我井边发生的一样
like the incident at my well.
我们打死了一个行尸
We put down a walker.
你们杀了一个人
You killed a person.
如果你看的广播和我看的一样
Well, if you watched the same broadcasts I did,
你应该看到行尸在袭击人类
You saw walkers attack,
残杀人类 他们很危险
kill. They're dangerous.
偏执性精神病也很危险
A paranoid schizophrenic is dangerous too.
我们不杀害病人
We don't shoot sick people.
无意冒犯
With all due respect,
但是你不了解外面的情况
you are cut off from the outside world here.
我亲眼见过我在乎的人死去
But I've seen people that I cared about.
变成了行尸
die and come back,
他们不是人
and they're not people.
我妻子和继子
My wife and stepson.
就在那个谷仓里
are in that barn.
他们是人
They're people.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
让我帮忙
Let me help.
我会和瑞克谈谈的 他是个好人
I'll speak to Rick. He's a good man.
我们可以加固谷仓 让大家更安全
We can make the barn more secure, keep everybody safe.
谷仓很安全
The barn is secure.
你想帮忙的话 不要告诉别人
Keep this to yourself if you want to help.
瑞克心地善良
Rick is a man of conscience,
但你确定所有你们的人都是这样吗
but are you so sure about everyone in your group?
下午好
Afternoon.
我想你孩子恢复得不错
I take it your boy did well.
挺好 真的
Not bad, actually.
你真应该庆幸自己没有女儿
Be grateful you don't have a daughter.
要是所有的事都像想去射击一样简单就好了
If only things were as simple as wanting to shoot.
卡尔有这样的机会 多亏了你
Carl's getting that chance, thanks to you.
我永远感激你对我们的帮助
And I'm eternally grateful.
和盛情款待
for what you did and your hospitality.
我们会干好我们的活
We'll earn our keep.
我很感谢 但是卡尔身体越来越好
I appreciate that, but with Carl getting better,
我想你们也该动身了
I imagine you'll be moving on soon…
听说你们要去本宁堡
Fort Benning, I hear.
- 没中 - 目标太小了
- Still a virgin. - The target's too small.
得了 别废话 半小时前
Come on, that's crap. Half-hour ago.
我亲眼见你射中了25尺外的靶心
I saw you nail a bull's-eye at 25'.
那个目标静止不动
It wasn't moving.
你以为行尸会站在那里等你打吗
You think a walker's gonna hold still for you?
专心点 装上子弹 再来一次
Focus and reload, go again.
我让你生气了吗
Uh-oh, did I piss you off?
快点 姑娘 你周围都是行尸
Come on, girl, you've got walkers all around you.
树林里 房车里
They're the woods. They're in the R.V.
你需要的不只是螺丝刀
You're gonna need more than a damn screwdriver.
- 别扰乱我 - 你太情绪化了
- Stop badgering me. - You're too damn emotional.
你得关闭自己的感觉 不要内疚
You need to shut it down. Take all that guilt,
不要恐惧 不要生气 统统不要
take that fear, that being pissed off, take it out.
对 你很平静
Right, 'cause you're so calm.
看到了吗 我可以很生气
See that? See, I can be pissed off.
我哼着迪克西（南北战争时期南方的战歌）也能打中目标
I could be whistling "Dixie" and I'll always hit the target.
但是你 老天 就像个小姑娘
But you, god, you shoot like a damn girl.
你站在这 拿枪指着行尸
You stand here and you point your weapon.
就像用你自己的手一样 什么都不要想
Point like you point your finger. Do not think about it.
我说的是肌肉记忆 姑娘
I'm talking about muscle memory, girl…
肌肉记忆
Muscle memory.
接着来 快打那个王八蛋
Now go on, shoot that son of a bitch.
他过来了 离你只有10尺
He's coming for you! He's 10 feet away!
9尺 只有5尺远了
He's 9 feet… he's 5 feet away!
就在那 就是那个行尸抓到了艾米
Right there, that's the walker that got Amy.
快打那个王八蛋 快打
Now you shoot that son of a bitch! Shoot him!
赫谢尔想让我们离开这
Hershel expects us to leave?
其他人知道这件事吗
Does anybody else know?
还不知道
Not yet.
- 你打算告诉我吗 - 当然
- Were you gonna tell me? - Of course.
什么时候 你知道多久了
When? How long have you known?
没多久 你不用担心这事
Not long. You don't need to worry about this.
我怎么可能不担心 这是我们的避难所
How can you expect me not to worry? We have shelter here.
有食物供给 还有医生照顾
and food and water and medical care.
我和赫谢尔说过了 这不是板上钉钉的事
I've been talking with Hershel. It's not carved in stone.
他觉得是
He thinks it is.
我们不能离开这
We have to fix this.
大家都习惯这的生活了 他们会吓坏的
People are settling in here. They'll be devastated.
我知道 我在处理
I know. I'm working on it.
也许我可以和他谈谈 求求情
Maybe I can talk to him too and plead our case.
不 不是那么简单 现在我们能做的
No, things are uneasy. The best thing right now.
就是给赫谢尔留些空间
is to give Hershel some space.
不要这样看着我
Don't look at me like that.
什么样
Like what?
好像你很害怕 你不信任我
Like you're scared. Like you don't trust me.
其他人这样我能接受 但你不行
I can take it from everyone else, but not from you.
我不明白
I don't understand how you could keep.
这事你为什么要瞒着我
something like this from me.
卡尔刚能下床 索菲亚也还没有找到
Carl's barely on his feet. And Sophia's missing.
达里尔和T仔都受了伤 我们怎么能走
And Daryl and T-dog are hurt. How can we leave?
我也不想离开这 但是如果我们必须得走
It's not what I want either, but if we have to go,
无论怎样我都要保证
I'll do whatever it takes to make sure.
你和卡尔没事再说
You and carl are okay.
我们会挺过去 会的
We'll get by. We will.
好吧
Okay.
上来吧 让我载你一程
Come on, let me give you a lift.
我的脚好的很
My feet work just fine.
我只是想吓吓你
Look, I'm just trying to get you rattled,
让你知道
Give you an idea.
乱世浮萍是什么感觉
What it's like when the shits starts to fly.
这是道歉吗
Is that an apology?
我不该提起艾米 我越线了
I crossed the line when I brought amy into it.
对 我是在向你道歉
Yeah, it's an apology.
有时候你就是个混蛋
You're a real dick sometimes.
我知道 听我说
Yeah, I acknowledge that. I'll tell you what:
我找到个关于索菲亚的线索 准备去查看下
I've got a lead on sophia. I'm gonna go check it out.
跟我一起去 做我的后援怎么样
Why don't you come with me, be my backup?
我妻子曾经有过一次身孕
My wife was pregnant once.
结果流产了
She miscarried.
之后我们就没再试过要孩子
And we didn't try again after that.
我很遗憾
I'm so sorry.
而我记得最清楚的是
The thing that I remember most.
她一闻到肉味
Is how nauseated she became.
就会觉得无比恶心
At the smell of cooking meat.
我妻子可是最喜欢吃肉的人啊
And she was a meat-eating gal… my wife,
然而一怀孕…
But with the pregnancy…
那个感恩节
That thanksgiving,
火鸡的味道…
The turkey…
整整两天她都不能待在家里
She couldn't be in the house.
直到味儿都散了
For two days until it was aired out,
可怜的老婆
Poor thing.
是格伦告诉你的吗
Glenn told you?
你以为是谁 这娃可没有坏心眼
What did you expect? The boy has no guile.
我还没告诉瑞克
I haven't told Rick.
说不出口
I can't.
和肖恩有关吗
Because of Shane?
有那么明显吗
Was it that obvious?
不 我觉得没人知道
No no, I don't think anyone knew.
我之前也不确定
I didn't, not for sure.
我以为我丈夫死了
Look, I thought my husband was dead.
当时觉得自己好像和他一起死掉了
And I felt like I died with him.
然后
And I…
我想找到活着的感觉 什么都行
I wanted to feel something… anything.
可是现在我恨死自己这么做了
And now I hate myself for it.
也恨肚里的孩子吗
And the baby?
孩子是瑞克的
It's Rick's.
除了这点其他的都没什么意义了
None of the rest of it matters.
那你为什么还担心
Then what's your concern?
现在是回忆让我继续坚持
Memories are what keep me going now.
过去生活的那些美好记忆
Memories of what life used to be.
我
And I…
我还有半辈子的美好记忆支撑着我
I've got a deep well to draw on.
还记得欢乐的模样
I still remember joy.
但是恐怕卡尔已经没什么可回忆的了
But I think carl's well is already running dry.
而肚里的这个孩子
And this baby…
它根本就不会有美好的记忆
The baby won't have any good memories at all,
只有恐惧和疼痛
Only fear and pain.
你不能这么想
You can't think like that.
我们仍然能找到欢乐
We can still find joy.
仍然能从彼此的身上找到力量
And we can still take strength from each other.
你真的认为这个孩子能有机会
Do you really think this baby has a chance,
长大成人并且过上幸福快乐的生活吗
That it could grow up and live a happy life?
看着我的眼睛告诉我
Look me in the eye and tell me.
我的孩子能够活到你这把年纪
That my baby will grow up to be your age.
并且快乐的离开这个世界
And die happy.
说啊 告诉我你坚信这一点
Tell me. Tell me you believe that.
对不起 我 说漏了嘴 好在是戴尔
I'm sorry. I'm… it just came out. And it was dale.
没事 我不该让你为难
It's okay. I never should have put you in that position.
你说我需要帮助的事
I've been thinking about what you said.
我考虑过了
About needing help.
你说的对 我真的需要帮助
And you're right that I do.
帮什么忙都行 真的
Name it. Yeah.
如果你还愿意为我进次城
If you're still willing to make a run into town for me…
我随叫随到
I'm your man.
谢谢你
Thank you.
别客气 小菜一碟 真的
It's okay. It's not a big deal really.
你没必要跟我来
You didn't have to come.
你可以远距离恨我
You could hate me from a distance.
拜托你开开金口
Please say something.
- 玛姬 我… - 我让你信任我 你却背叛了它
- Maggie, I… - I asked for your trust and you betrayed it.
现在我爸生我的气了
Now my dad's pissed at me.
你说吧
Your turn.
你爸认为他们生病了？
So your dad thinks they're sick?
你认同这种说法吗
You agree with that?
即使在井边事件之后还这么认为吗
Even after what you saw at the well?
我不确定当时在井边看到了什么
I'm not sure what I saw at the well.
不 你确定
Yes, you are.
听着 如果你去过亚特兰大
Look, if you'd seen Atlanta,
你就不会圈一谷仓的行尸了
You would not have a barn full of walkers.
我希望你能停止这么叫他们
I wish you'd stop calling them that.
那你怎么称呼他们
What do you call them?
妈妈
Mom,
沙恩
Shawn,
费希尔先生 费希尔太太 莱茜 邓肯
Mr. And mrs. Fischer, Lacey, Duncan.
她这次又想要什么
What does she want now?
我不能说
I can't say.
所以当他们中的一个人让你保密时
So when one of them asks you to keep your mouth shut…
求你别墨迹了
Crawl out of my butt.
赶紧帮我找吧
And help me look, please.
你玩我呢吧
You've got to be kidding me.
不
No!
不 不
No! No!
格伦
Glenn!
- 玛姬 - 格伦 救我
- Maggie! - Glenn, help me!
格伦 救我
Help! Glenn!
把他弄走 救命
Get it off me! Help!
它伤着你了吗 咬到你没
Did it get you? Did it bite you?
格伦
Glenn.
我们得挨家挨户找
We're gonna have to go house to house.
从最远一家开始 然后往回找
We'll start at the far end and we'll work our way back.
要是索菲亚能走到这 活着的机会就很大
If Sophia got this far, she has a real shot,
你觉得呢
Don't you think?
喂 我们拿到了你要的东西
Hey! We got your stuff.
玛姬 等下 求你
Maggie, hang on, please.
到里面来
Come on in here.
为什么 别藏着掖着 你的特快专递在这里
Why? Nothing to hide. We got your special delivery right here.
你要的乳液 护发素
We got your lotion, got your conditioner,
- 你的肥皂剧杂志 - 玛姬
- Your soap opera digest. - Maggie.
下次你想要什么东西 你他妈的自己去
Next time you want something, get it your damn self.
- 我们不是你跑腿的 - 亲爱的我
- We're not your errand boys. - Honey, I…
还有这是你的打胎药
And here's your abortion pills.
- 那件事做的不太对 - 哪件事不对
- That was not cool. - Which part?
那个贱人差点让我俩送命的事吗
The part where that bitch almost got us killed?
我应该自己去
I should've gone alone.
如果你想怪谁的话 就怪我吧
If you want to blame anybody, blame me.
是啊 把错揽到自己身上
Right, take the blame.
知道吗 作为一个聪明人你真是笨到家了
You know, for a smart guy, you're really stupid.
好吧 我有点糊涂了
Okay, I'm confused,
因为我以为你刚
Because I think you just.
称赞了我 可是听起来又
paid me a compliment, but you made it s…
我已经失去了这世界上
I've already lost three of the people.
我最在乎的三个人
That I care about most in this world.
- 玛姬 - 闭嘴
- Maggie… - shut up.
你人聪明 又勇敢
You're smart. You're brave.
你是个领袖 但是你自己不知道
You're a leader. But you don't know it.
而你的朋友不想知道这点
And your friends don't want to know it.
他们更愿意让你去找桃子
They'd rather have you fetching peaches.
井里有个行尸 让格伦下去
There's a dead guy in the well? Send glenn down.
你是钓行尸的诱饵
You're walker bait.
我不想看你变成像他们一样
I can't take you becoming one of them.
索菲亚
Sophia?
有人吗
Anyone?
索菲亚
Sophia?
他们用墙把走廊隔开了是吗
They walled off the hallway?
他们尝试留在这里
They tried to make a stand here.
索菲亚
Sophia?
她没来过这儿
She was never here,
对吧
Was she?
我不知该怎么告诉卡萝尔线索又断了
I don't know how to tell Carol this was another dead end.
快点 快走
Come on, let's move.
你负责街上的行尸 我负责车周围的
Cover that street. I'll clear the car.
糟了
Oh shit.
集中精神 把枪弄好 集中精神
Focus now. Clear the jam. Focus.
- 你开什么玩笑啊 - 有我呢 放心杀吧
- Are you kidding me? - I got your back. Go.
安德莉亚 安德莉亚 快走
Andrea, Andrea, let's go.
快
Come on.
安德莉亚 快点
Andrea, come on.
玛姬衣服上有血
The blood on Maggie's shirt…
她被袭击了
She was attacked.
你们没事吧 情况严重吗
Are you guys all right? How bad was it?
险些没命
It was pretty close.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我不该叫你去的
I should never have asked you to go.
我自愿的
I offered.
我以为镇里很安全 可如果你们回不来
I thought the town was safe, but if you hadn't come back…
可我们回来了 我总能脱险
But we did. I always do.
那些紧急避孕药有效吗
The morning-after pills… will they even work?
我也不知道
I don't know.
我不知道自己是否希望它们有效
And I don't know if I want them to.
我还弄了些这个
Then I got these too,
以防万一
Just in case.
产前维生素
Prenatal vitamins.
这事太难决定了
That's a hell of a choice.
幸好我不用想这种事
I'm glad it's not mine.
洛莉 我们是朋友 对吧
Lori, we're friends, aren't we?
经历了这么多 我们当然是朋友
With everything we've been through… yeah.
我没法教你怎么做
I can't tell you what to do.
这种事我没法教你
I could never tell you something like that.
但这件事
But your choice…
也许你不该私自下决定
Maybe you shouldn't make it alone.
放马来吧
Come on then.
快上来 快上来
Get over here. Get over here.
有发现吗
Anything?
还没有
Not today.
我很遗憾
I'm so sorry.
我们明天会搜索更多地方
We'll cover more ground tomorrow.
你们碰上什么事了
What happened out there?
我呃
Um, I…
- 那地方丧尸暴走了 - 是啊
- The place was overrun. - Yeah.
去洗洗干净吧
Let's go get you cleaned up.
肖恩 肖恩
Shane, shane,
我在想 你给自己弄了台新车
I was thinking, you've got that nice new ride of yours,
装满了油 足够让你远走高飞了
plenty of fuel, more than enough for you to get far from here.
怎么 你要我走吗
What, you telling me to leave?
我知道你有此计划
I know you've been planning to.
也许现在正是时机
Maybe now is a good time.
是因为安德莉亚吗
Is this about Andrea?
我是为了大家着想
I'm looking out for the group.
戴尔 你觉得没了我 大家会过得更好是吗
You think the group would be better off without me, Dale?
你怎么不跟瑞克和洛莉说去
Why don't you tell that to Rick or Lori?
要不是老子 他们的儿子早没命了
Their boy would be dead if I hadn't put my ass on the line.
还有奥蒂斯
And Otis's.
你对那晚发生的事一直含糊其辞
You've been vague about that night, about what happened.
奥蒂斯是英勇牺牲的
Otis died a hero.
这话你说过
So you've said.
正是那晚的牺牲 才挽救了一个孩子
A little boy lived because of what went down that night.
我觉得你应该心存感恩
I think you ought to show some gratitude.
- 我当时不在场 - 是啊 你根本不在
- I wasn't there. - No, man, you weren't.
不过你用枪指着瑞克时 我可看得一清二楚
But I was the time that you raised your gun on Rick.
- 拜托 老天 - 你清楚地看到是他
- Come on. Jesus. - You had him in your sights.
而你却用枪指着他
And you held him there.
我知道你是什么样的人
I know what kind of man you are.
你以为我会朝瑞克开枪吗
You think I'd shoot Rick?
他是我最好的朋友
That is my best friend.
我爱这兄弟
That's the man that I love.
就像爱自己的亲兄弟一样
I love him like he's my a brother.
你以为我是那种人吗
You think that's the kind of man I am?
没错
That's right.
那也许我们得想想清楚
Well, maybe we ought to just think that through.
如果说我是那种
Say I'm the kind of man.
会杀自己最好的朋友的人
Who'd gun down his own best friend.
如果我不喜欢的人开始指控我
What do you think I'd do to some guy that I don't even like.
你觉得我会怎么做
when he starts throwing accusations my way?
你怎么想
What do you think?
你有什么事需要告诉我吗
Is there something you need to tell me?
我们不能走 我怀孕了
We can't leave. I'm pregnant.
是吗
Are you?
我吐出来了
I threw them up.
你尽管骂吧
You can yell if you want.
如果想喊就喊出来吧 但请你
You can scream if you have to, but…
跟我谈谈
talk to me.
你知道多久了
How long have you known?
这要紧吗
Does it matter?
几天吗 几周吗 你却瞒着我
Days? Weeks? And you didn't tell me?
- 我正要告诉你 - 不对
- I'm telling you now. - No.
我找到了这些药
I found these.
这么说 格兰知道 对吧
So glenn knows, right?
你让他去弄药 而不是来找我
Instead of going to me, you sent him to get pills?
我慌了 因为你说我们现在居无定所
I panicked. You tell me we have no roof and no walls…
别跟我说这个
Do not put this on me!
你冲我发火
You tear into me for.
就因为你守着这秘密 还吃这玩意儿
keeping secrets when you're holding onto this?
你想让孩子生在这种环境下吗
You want me to bring a baby into this?
让他茹毛饮血 朝不保夕
To live a short, cruel life?
你怎么能这么想
How can you think like that?
我们连现有的孩子都保护不了
We can't even protect the son we already have.
那你就这么解决吗
So this is the solution?
瑞克 我都吐出来了
Rick, I threw them up.
是我不好
I screwed up.
我不知道我们该怎么办
I don't know how we do this.
我们能行
We can make it work.
怎么做 你说啊
How? Tell me how.
我们会想出办法的
We'll figure it out.
难道我们不该试着想办法吗
Shouldn't we try to figure it out?
你把药吐出来了
You threw up the pills.
你想保住孩子 我知道
You want this baby. I know you do.
可不能像这样
Not like this.
我不能在这荒郊野岭生下他
Not giving birth in a ditch.
不能让他打娘胎里出来就朝不保夕
Not when its life will hang by a thread from the second it's born.
不能让他的每一声哭泣都把他
Not when every cry will put it,
把卡尔 把所有我们关心的人都置于险境
and Carl, and everyone we care about, in danger.
不能这样
That's not right.
可也不能剥夺他生存的机会啊
Not even giving it a chance isn't right either.
也许这就是为什么我不想告诉你
Maybe this is why I didn't want to tell you.
我还是 还是不明白为什么
I still… I still don't understand why.
你真的觉得我会逼你生孩子吗
You really think I'd make you have a baby you don't want?
不 如果我真的把胎儿打掉
No, so that if I went through with it,
良心受谴责的就是我 而不是你
it would be on my conscience and not yours.
也许确实如此 可是
Maybe that's true, but.
我不能再这么生活了
I can't live like this anymore,
洛莉
Lori.
我们不能这么生活
We can't live like this.
还有什么别的事要告诉我的吗
Is there anything else I should know about?
肖恩和我
Shane and I.
我知道 我当然知道
I know. Of course I know.
你以为我死了
You thought I was dead.
这世界操蛋了 你以为我死了
The world went to shit and you thought I was dead.
对吧
Right?
是啊
Yeah.